grapevinelogic.com 2019-05-10

# YouTube Influencer Marketing | Grapevine

## Privacy Policy

Grapevine Logic takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. The federal government and technology industry have developed practical tips to help you guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer and protect your personal information.

### INFORMATION AND COLLECTION OF USE

Grapevine Logic collects personal information when you register on GrapevineLogic.com. Grapevine Logic may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your name and email address. When you register with Grapevine Logic and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Grapevine Logic automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, Grapevine Logic cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

#### Your Youtube Account

When you connect your YouTube account to your Grapevine Logic account, we use the YouTube API to automatically collect and store information about your channel including profile information such as your name channel performance measures such as views, likes, dislikes on your channel and videos and demographic information about your subscriber base such gender, age, and geographic breakdown.

Please review YouTube's own privacy policy to learn more about how YouTube protects your privacy and allows you to limit what information you share. <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy>

You may revoke Grapevine's access to your YouTube data [here](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions) at any time.

Grapevine Logic uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, and conduct research. You may set up a profile on Grapevine Logic.

Grapevine Logic may collect the following information, but not limited to:

  * Contact information such as name, address, postal code, e-mail address and telephone number;
  * Social media profile information such as username and other profile data;
  * Demographic information such as gender, age, and occupation, and location;
  * Personal information, including the information you may transmit to us or authorize us to obtain from you or a third party in connection with the Services ("Customer Data").

### INFORMATION SHARING

Grapevine Logic does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or when we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. If Grapevine Logic becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### COOKIES

As you browse Grapevinelogic.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with Grapevinelogic.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number. You can visit [this page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of AdRoll's and their partners' targeted advertising.

### NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

This is information that is commonly made available by web browsers and servers, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Grapevine Logic uses this information to understand how visitors use our website.

### CONTENTS OF ITEMS

The contents of any item that you post directly to the Site, including any text, images, photos, videos and audio, are stored and maintained on our servers in order to publish these items and provide the Service. Your submitted content will be associated with your account.

### CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

### THIRD PARTY SITES

This Policy only applies to the Grapevine Logic website and services. We do not exercise control over the sites that our service links to. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and Grapevine Logic shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

### DATA INTEGRITY

Grapevine Logic processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Grapevine Logic may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Grapevine Logic account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
